#### Contact

16th, Issac Road, Near Anantpura Gate, Puttenahalli Village, Yelahanka 9380611436 (Home) tusharpandey13@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tushar-pandey-376a51134 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Node.js
REST API

## Languages

English (Professional Working)

### Certifications

Google Cloud Platform Essentials Perform Sentiment Analysis with scikit-learn

# **Tushar Pandey**

Backend Intern at IBM Global Remote Mentoring Program | DSC-BMSIT student member

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

# Summary

Hi! I'm a student at BMSIT. I have experience with python and Node.js, linux systems and computer vision.

I'm an easygoing and decent guy and I love to meet new people and make friends.

For information about my projects you can visit my github! (@tusharpandey13)

# Experience

IBM Global Remote Mentoring Program Backend Intern April 2020 - Present (3 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka

Worked as a backend intern at IBM Global Remote Mentoring Program for the project Data Readiness Toolkit

urbanstop

Backend Intern

November 2019 - December 2019 (2 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Worked as an Intern for backend REST API development. Was responsible for the successful development, testing and deployment of various RESTful API services across the client system. Learned essential skills like team-player and time management.

# Education

BMS Institute of Technology and Management
Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Science · (2018 - 2022)

Delhi Public School, Dhanbad

High School Diploma, Computer Science · (2006 - 2018)